Guide to the Tristan Taormino papers, 1989-2014.
Taormino, Tristan papers
- Series III. Publications
  - Books, Magazines, & Related Materials
    - Opening Up
      - OU Interviews: Dom + Aeran, 2004-2005; CD-3418 (Box 20)
        Disk 20
      - OU Interviews: Brian D + Mika, 2004-2005; CD-3419 (Box 20)
        Disk 21
      - OU Interviews: Kevin / Cori / Rose, 2004-2005; CD-3420 (Box 20)
        Disk 22
      - OU Interviews: Shervon + Brian, 2004-2005; CD-3421 (Box 20)
        Disk 23
      - OU Interviews: Scott, Amanda, Leah, 2004-2005; CD-3422 (Box 20)
        Disk 24
      - OU Interviews: Bitsy, Matt, Henry, 2004-2005; CD-3423 (Box 20)
        Disk 25
      - OU Interviews: Laura C, 2004-2005; CD-3424 (Box 20)
        Disk 26
      - OU Interviews: Jill, 2004-2005; CD-3425 (Box 20)
        Disk 27
      - OU Interviews: Anita + Tim, 2004-2005; CD-3426 (Box 20)
        Disk 28
      - OU Interviews: Sarah S, 2004-2005; CD-3427 (Box 20)
        Disk 29
      - OU Interviews: Michael, Rob, Tim Part 1, 2004-2005; CD-3428 (Box 20)
        Disk 30
      - OU Interviews: Michael, Rob, Tim Part 2 + Jefferson, 2004-2005; CD-3429 (Box 20)
        Disk 31
    - Pucker Up Magazine
      - Pucker Up magazine photos, 1993-1996 (Box 14, Folder 32)
      - Pucker Up Contracts, 1993-1997 (Box 14, Folder 33)
        Includes contributor and model contracts
      - Pucker Up magazine, 1994-11-1996-07 (Box 14, Folder 34)
        Includes correspondence, promotional materials, publishing information and proofs, business materials
      - Pucker Up magazine, 1995-12-1996-12 (Box 14, Folder 35)
        Vol. 1 No. 1-4
    - Best Lesbian Erotica
      - Best Lesbian Erotica, 1996-2009 (Box 14, Folder 36)
      - Best Lesbian Erotica Barnes & Noble poster, 1996-06-28 (Mapcase-folder 4)
      - Best Lesbian Erotica cover, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 37)
        Edited by Tristan Taormino
      - Best Lesbian Erotica Barnes & Noble poster, 1997-06-12 (Mapcase-folder 4)
  - Conference Materials
    - Out Write programs, 1995-03-03-1998-02-22 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      Lesbian and Gay Writers Conference
    - Out Write, 1998-01-1998-02; Taormino, Tristan (Box 14, Folder 2)
      Lesbian and Gay Writers Conference; Includes materials for talk "Creating Queer Canons"
    - Event name badges, 1998-04-2001-09 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Conference materials, 1998-08-2010-04 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      Includes programs and promotional materials for every conference attended by Tristan Taormino; topics include: queer, LGBT writers, BDSM, polyamory, porn, etc.
    - International Drag King Extravaganza materials, 1999-02-2002-08 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      Includes correspondence, programs, article clippings, flyers
    - Michigan Womyn's Music Festival, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      Includes programs, articles, and materials for Camp Trans a simultaneous event started in response to the views expressed by Michigan Womyn's Music Festival organizers
    - Conference materials, 2001-06-2013-06 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Promotional Materials
    - Flyer/Promo Pieces, 1993-02-2004 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Promotional quarter cards, 1996-2010 (Box 14, Folder 29)
      Includes cards for Pucker Up, Opening Up, True Lust, Expert Guide to Female Orgasms, lectures and workshops, Backdoor Betty book release parties, She Hate Me movie
    - Tristan Taormino resume, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Event flyers, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - The Path to Sexual Empowerment poster, 2008-04-16 (Mapcase-folder 1)
      Sexpo event, held at University of Wisconsin - Milwaukee
    - Posters from events, 1995-2012 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Chemistry posters, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Count: 2
    - Rough Sex 3: Adriana's Dangerous Mind poster, 2011 (Mapcase-folder 2)
      Signed by Jiz Lee and Danny Wylde; count: 2
    - Ultimate Guide to Anal Sex for Women jacket, 1999; MU-1768 (Box 18)
    - Puckerup.com can cozy, Undated; MU-1769 (Box 18)
    - House of Ass drinking glass, 2006; MU-1770 (Box 18)
    - Anal sex mousepads, Undated; MU-1774-1775 (Box 18)
    - Anal sex coffee mugs, Undated; MU-1776-1777 (Box 18)
    - Puckerup.com cap, Undated; MU-1778 (Box 18)
    - Anal sex t-shirts, Undated; MU-1779-1780 (Box 18)
    - Assorted buttons on sexuality, Undated; MU-1787-1795 (Box 18)
    - Puckerup.com website, 1996-2004-02 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Puckerup.com website redesign, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Series VI. Public Appearances & Related Materials
  - Workshops & Lectures
    - Lecture materials, 1998-03-2013-02 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      Includes correspondence, notes, printouts of lectures
    - Workshop materials, 1998-03-18-1999-02 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      Includes correspondence, notes, promotional materials, talk outlines
    - Tristan Taormino at Wesleyan University, 2009-04; DVD-2117 (Box 8)
    - Lesbian Sex & Sexuality: Selling Sex to the Mainstream, 2007-01-23; DVD-2118 (Box 8)
    - Workshop handouts from others, 1998-2013 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - American Federation of Television and Radio Artists Union Card, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Radio
    - Alan Colmes Show, Undated; tr-11663 (Box 8)
      Guests included Tristan Taormino, Alicia Colon, and Rich Miniter
    - Tristan + Stern, 2004; tr-11664 (Box 8)
      WXRK 92.3 FM
    - Tristan Taormino on Howard Stern, 1997-12-09; tr-11665 (Box 8)
    - Loveline Part 1 & 2, 1998-04-09; tr-11666 (Box 8)
    - Loveline Part 3, 1998-04-09; tr-11667 (Box 8)
    - WNYC pilot, Undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
      Tristan Taormino's Public Radio Show About Sex
  - Television
    - The Ricki Lake Show
      - "Fast" Women, 2002-2003; V-9760 (Box 8)
        Show #10040
      - I Can't Get Sex Satisfaction!, 2002-2003; V-9761 (Box 8)
        Show #10048
      - My Man Can't Do It!, 2002-2003; V-9762 (Box 8)
        Show #10074
      - Sex Secrets!, 2002-2003; V-9763 (Box 8)
        Show #10086
      - Divas Get Dissed On Tape!, 2002-2003; V-9764 (Box 8)
        Show #10087
      - Stop Hating My Man!, 2002-2003; V-9765 (Box 8)
        Show #10092
      - Please Sleep with Me Now!, 2002-2003; V-9766 (Box 8)
        Show #10099
      - Women Who Can't Let Go, 2002-09-17; V-9767 (Box 8)
        Show #10004
      - Sleeping with Younger Men!, 2002-09-18; V-9768 (Box 8)
        Show #10009
      - Strangers in Our Bed, 2002-10; V-9769 (Box 8)
        Show #10010
      - Threesomes, 2002-10; V-9770 (Box 8)
        Duplicate of "Strangers in Our Bed"
      - We've Lost Our Mojo, 2003-01-15; V-9771 (Box 8)
        Show #10033
      - Getting the Mojo Back, 2003-01-15; V-9772 (Box 8)
        Duplicate of "We've Lost Our Mojo"
      - Gals Who Love Gays, 2003-04-09; V-9773 (Box 8)
        Show #10035
      - Sexually Frustrated Couples, 2003-04-19; V-9774 (Box 8)
      - Bisexuals Exposed, 2003-04-28; V-9775 (Box 8)
        Show #10098
      - Sister Slumber Party!, 2003-05-06; V-9776 (Box 8)
        Show #10115
    - Other Appearances
      - CNN Sunday Night, 2003-06-22; V-9777 (Box 8)
        Interview along with Dan Savage about the impact of "Sex and the City"
      - SexTV: On Our Backs, 1999-11-27; V-9778 (Box 8)
        Includes profile of lesbian erotica magazine On Our Backs
      - SexTV Profile, 2001-10; V-9779 (Box 8)
      - SexTV, Undated; V-9780 (Box 8)
      - Five Compilation: Whatever Turns You On Ep 1/2/3, Undated; V-9781 (Box 8)
      - Lesbian Central, Undated; V-9782 (Box 8)
      - The Great Big Drag King Show, 2001-05-19; V-9783 (Box 8)
      - Sex Files: Rear End, 2001-06; V-9784 (Box 8)
        Discovery Channel
      - Fox News: Flesh, Inc., 2001-07-21; V-9785 (Box 8)
        Fox News
      - The Other Half: Tristan Taormino, 2001-11-02; V-9786 (Box 8)
        NBC
      - Howard Stern: Anal Sex Author, 2002-04-03; V-9787 (Box 8)
      - Pucker Up, 2002-05-31; V-9788 (Box 8)
        Oxygen Media
      - Tristan Taormino Presentation Tape, 2003-04; V-9789 (Box 8)
        MTV
      - Tristan Taormino, 2003-06-16; V-9790 (Box 8)
      - Real Sex: Am I Good in Bed?, 2003-11-22; V-9791 (Box 8)
        Episode 31
        HBO
      - The Big Idea with Donny Deutsch, 2005-2008; V-9792 (Box 8)
      - Howard Stern: Tristan Taormino, 2006-04-05; V-9795 (Box 8)
      - Sexology Show, 2000-12-2001-01 (Box 12, Folder 24)
        Includes notes regarding topic segments and casting for new show on Burly Bear Network
      - Sexology Episode 1, 2001; V-9796 (Box 8)
        Burly Bear Network
      - Sexology Episode 2, 2001; V-9797 (Box 8)
      - Sexology Episode 3, 2001; V-9798 (Box 8)
      - Fox News: Hotel Quickies, 2000-02; V-9799 (Box 8)
      - Hips, Lips, & Genderbenders: MTV's History of Sex, 2001-01; V-9800 (Box 8)
      - The Naughty Show rough cut, 2003-09-04; V-9801 (Box 8)
        Never aired
      - The Naughty Show rough cut, 2003-09-09; V-9802 (Box 8)
      - The Naughty Show rough cut, 2003-09-11; V-9803 (Box 8)
      - Real Sex: Strut You Strap-On, 2000-06-17; V-9804 (Box 8)
        Episode 25
      - Naked New York, 2002-12-23; V-9805 (Box 8)
      - Tristan Taormino, Undated; V-9806-9807 (Box 8)
        Contains media clips
      - A Girl's Guide to Taking Over the World, 1997-09-03; V-9809 (Box 8)
        First edition, aired on Good Day New York
      - A Girl's Guide to Taking Over the World, 1997-11-06; V-9810 (Box 8)
        Aired on NJ Channel 12
      - Tristan Taormino, 2003-06-16; V-9811; DVCAM (Box 8)
- Series V. Projects
  - Smart Ass Productions
    - Final Versions/Commercial Copies
      - Vivid Entertainment scripts, 2004-2011 (Box 12, Folder 25)
      - Chemistry, 2006-05; DVD-2124-2125 (Box 9)
        2 discs
        Smart Ass Productions
        Vivid Entertainment
      - Chemistry Vol. 2, 2006-05; DVD-2126-2127 (Box 9)
      - Chemistry Vol. 3, 2006-10; DVD-2320-2321 (Box 9)
      - Expert Guide to Oral Sex, Part 1: Cunnilingus, 2006-10; DVD-2130-2131 (Box 9)
        Written and directed by Tristan Taormino
      - Expert Guide to Anal Sex, 2007-02; DVD-2132-2133 (Box 9)
      - Chemistry Vol. 4, 2007-05; DVD-2322-2323 (Box 9)
      - Expert Guide to Female Ejaculation, 2007-05-2010-05; DVD-2128-2129 (Box 9)
      - Expert Guide to the G Spot, 2007-05; DVD-2134-2135 (Box 9)
      - Expert Guide to Oral Sex, Part 2: Fellatio, 2007-06; DVD-2156-2157 (Box 9)
      - Expert Guide to Positions, 2008-02; DVD-2136-2137 (Box 9)
        Directed by Geoff Bean
      - Expert Guide to Threesomes, 2008-02; DVD-2138-2139 (Box 9)
      - Expert Guide to Hand Jobs for Men & Women, 2008-02; DVD-2140-2141 (Box 9)
        Written and directed by Tristan Taormino & Penny Flame
      - Expert Guide to Sensual Bondage, 2008-08; DVD-2142-2143 (Box 9)
        Directed by Tristan Taormino
      - Expert Guide to Rough Sex, 2008-08; DVD-2144-2145 (Box 9)
        Written and directed by Penny Flame
      - Expert Guide to Anal Pleasure for Men, 2008-08; DVD-2158-2159 (Box 9)
      - Rough Sex, 2008-08; DVD-2160-2161 (Box 9)
      - Expert Guide to Advanced Fellatio, 2009-05; DVD-2146-2147 (Box 9)
      - Rough Sex 2, 2009-05; DVD-2162-2163 (Box 9)
      - Expert Guide to Female Orgasms, 2010-05; DVD-2148-2149 (Box 9)
      - Expert Guide to Advanced Anal Sex, 2010-05; DVD-2150-2151 (Box 9)
      - Rough Sex 3: Adrianna's Dangerous Mind, 2010-05; DVD-2164-2165 (Box 9)
      - Expert Guide to Pegging, 2011-04; DVD-2152 (Box 9)
      - Vivid Entertainment production book, 2008-01-2010-05; Taormino, Tristan (Box 15)
        Includes sections on the films: Threesomes, Hand Jobs, Positions, Rough Sex, Advanced Fellatio, Advanced Anal, Rough Sex 3, Female Ejaculation, Female Orgasm
      - Vivid Entertainment production book, 2004-09-2010-05; Taormino, Tristan (Box 16)
        Includes sections on the films: Advanced Anal, Female Ejaculation, Female Orgasm, Rough Sex 3, Miscellaneous, Hand Job, Positions, Threesome, Bondage, Anal for Men, Rough Sex, Penny's Rough Sex, Advanced Fellatio, Rough Sex 2
      - Chemistry Vol. 1 & Chemistry Vol. 2 production book, 2006-04-2006-05; Taormino, Tristan (Box 17)
        13 STD laboratory test results for chlamydia, gonorrhea, and HIV-1 were removed to protect paitents' privacy
    - Rough Footage
      - Rough Sex Casting Tape 1, 2008; DVD-2166 (Box 20)
      - Rough Sex Casting Tape 2, 2008; DVD-2167 (Box 20)
      - Rough Sex Casting Tape 3, 2008; DVD-2168 (Box 20)
      - Rough Sex Casting Tape 4, 2008; DVD-2169 (Box 20)
      - Rough Sex Csating Day 2 Tape 1, 2008; DVD-2170 (Box 20)
      - Rough Sex Csating Day 2 Tape 2, 2008; DVD-2171 (Box 20)
      - Expert Guide to Hand Jobs Screener, 2008; DVD-2172-2173 (Box 20)
      - Hand Jobs Tape A2, 2008; DVD-2174 (Box 20)
      - Hand Jobs Tape A3, 2008; DVD-2175 (Box 20)
      - Hand Jobs Tape B2, 2008; DVD-2176 (Box 20)
      - Hand Jobs Tape B3, 2008; DVD-2177 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 4 Edit 2, 2007-2008; DVD-2178 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 4 XXX First Cut, 2008-03-07; DVD-2179 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 4 Confessional Roll A1, 2007-2008; DVD-2180 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 4 Roll A2, 2007-2008; DVD-2181 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 4 Roll A3, 2007-2008; DVD-2182 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 4 Confessional Roll A4, 2007-2008; DVD-2183 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 4 Roll A5, 2007-2008; DVD-2184 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 4 Roll A6, 2007-2008; DVD-2185 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 4 Confessional Roll A7, 2007-2008; DVD-2186 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 4 Confessional Roll A8, 2007-2008; DVD-2187 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 4 Confessional Roll A9, 2007-2008; DVD-2188 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 4 Roll A10, 2007-2008; DVD-2189 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 4 Roll A11, 2007-2008; DVD-2190 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 4 Roll A12, 2007-2008; DVD-2191 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 4 Roll B1, 2007-2008; DVD-2192 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 4 Roll B2, 2007-2008; DVD-2193 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 4 Roll B3, 2007-2008; DVD-2194 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 4 Roll B4, 2007-2008; DVD-2195 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 4 Roll B5, 2007-2008; DVD-2196 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 4 Roll B6, 2007-2008; DVD-2197 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 4 Perv Cam Roll C1, 2007-2008; DVD-2198 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 4 Perv Cam Roll C2, 2007-2008; DVD-2199 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 4 Perv Cam Roll C3, 2007-2008; DVD-2200 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 4 Perv Cam Roll C4, 2007-2008; DVD-2201 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 4 Perv Cam Roll C5, 2007-2008; DVD-2202 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 4 Perv Cam Roll C6, 2007-2008; DVD-2203 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 4 Perv Cam - Photoshoot, 2007-2008; DVD-2204 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 4 Photoshoot, 2007-2008; DVD-2205 (Box 20)
      - ChemistryVol. 3 Screener 1, 2006; DVD-2206 (Box 20)
      - ChemistryVol. 3 Screener 2, 2006; DVD-2207 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 3 A Cam Tape 1, 2006; DVD-2208 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 3 A Cam Tape 2, 2006; DVD-2209 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 3 A Cam Tape 3, 2006; DVD-2210 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 3 A Cam Tape 4, 2006; DVD-2211 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 3 A Cam Tape 5, 2006; DVD-2212 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 3 A Cam Tape 6, 2006; DVD-2213 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 3 B Cam Tape 1, 2006; DVD-2214 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 3 B Cam Tape 2, 2006; DVD-2215 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 3 B Cam Tape 3, 2006; DVD-2216 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 3 B Cam Tape 4, 2006; DVD-2217 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 3 B Cam Tape 5, 2006; DVD-2218 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 3 B Cam Tape 6, 2006; DVD-2219 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 3 B Cam Tape 7, 2006; DVD-2220 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 3 B Cam Tape 8, 2006; DVD-2221 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 3 C Cam Tape 1, 2006; DVD-2222 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 3 C Cam Tape 2, 2006; DVD-2223 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 3 C Cam Tape 3, 2006; DVD-2224 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 3 C Cam Tape 4, 2006; DVD-2225 (Box 20)
      - Expert G-Spot Tape A1, 2007; DVD-2226 (Box 20)
      - Expert G-Spot Tape A2, 2007; DVD-2227 (Box 20)
      - Expert G-Spot Tape A3, 2007; DVD-2228 (Box 20)
      - Expert G-Spot Tape A4, 2007; DVD-2229 (Box 20)
      - Expert G-Spot Tape A5, 2007; DVD-2230 (Box 20)
      - Expert G-Spot Tape A6, 2007; DVD-2231 (Box 20)
      - Expert G-Spot Tape B1, 2007; DVD-2232 (Box 20)
      - Expert G-Spot Tape B2, 2007; DVD-2233 (Box 20)
      - Expert G-Spot Tape B3, 2007; DVD-2234 (Box 20)
      - Expert G-Spot Tape B4, 2007; DVD-2235 (Box 20)
      - Expert G-Spot Tape B5, 2007; DVD-2236 (Box 20)
      - Expert Oral 2 Fellatio A1, 2007; DVD-2237 (Box 20)
      - Expert Oral 2 Fellatio A2, 2007; DVD-2238 (Box 20)
      - Expert Oral 2 Fellatio A3, 2007; DVD-2239 (Box 20)
      - Expert Oral 2 Fellatio A4, 2007; DVD-2240 (Box 20)
      - Expert Oral 2 Fellatio A5, 2007; DVD-2241 (Box 20)
      - Expert Oral 2 Fellatio B1, 2007; DVD-2242 (Box 20)
      - Expert Oral 2 Fellatio B2, 2007; DVD-2243 (Box 20)
      - Expert Oral 2 Fellatio B3, 2007; DVD-2244 (Box 20)
      - Expert Oral 2 Fellatio B4, 2007; DVD-2245 (Box 20)
      - Expert Oral 2 Fellatio B5, 2007; DVD-2246 (Box 20)
      - Expert Oral 2 Fellatio B6, 2007; DVD-2247 (Box 20)
      - Expert Oral 2 Fellatio VO, 2007; DVD-2248 (Box 20)
      - Expert Oral 2 Fellatio Bonus, 2007; DVD-2249 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 2 Pass 1, 2006; DVD-2250 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 2 Roughcut 2, 2006; DVD-2251 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 2 A1, 2006; DVD-2252 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 2 A2, 2006; DVD-2253 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 2 A3, 2006; DVD-2254 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 2 A4, 2006; DVD-2255 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 2 A5, 2006; DVD-2256 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 2 B1, 2006; DVD-2257 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 2 B2, 2006; DVD-2258 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 2 B3, 2006; DVD-2259 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 2 B4, 2006; DVD-2260 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 2 B5, 2006; DVD-2261 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 2 B6, 2006; DVD-2262 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 2 B7, 2006; DVD-2263 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 2 B8, 2006; DVD-2264 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 2 C1, 2006; DVD-2265 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 2 C2, 2006; DVD-2266 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 2 C3, 2006; DVD-2267 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 2 C4, 2006; DVD-2268 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 1 Pass 1 Bonus Material, 2006; DVD-2269 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 1 Pass 1 Disk 1, 2006; DVD-2270 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 1 Pass 1 Disk 2, 2006; DVD-2271 (Box 20)
      - Chemistry Vol. 1 Pass 1 Disk 3, 2006; DVD-2272 (Box 20)
      - Expert Oral 1 Cunnilingus A1, 2006-2007; DVD-2273 (Box 20)
      - Expert Oral 1 Cunnilingus A2, 2006-2007; DVD-2274 (Box 20)
      - Expert Oral 1 Cunnilingus A3, 2006-2007; DVD-2275 (Box 20)
      - Expert Oral 1 Cunnilingus A4, 2006-2007; DVD-2276 (Box 20)
      - Expert Oral 1 Cunnilingus A5, 2006-2007; DVD-2277 (Box 20)
      - Expert Oral 1 Cunnilingus A6, 2006-2007; DVD-2278 (Box 20)
      - Expert Oral 1 Cunnilingus B1, 2006-2007; DVD-2279 (Box 20)
      - Expert Oral 1 Cunnilingus B2, 2006-2007; DVD-2280 (Box 20)
      - Expert Oral 1 Cunnilingus B3, 2006-2007; DVD-2281 (Box 20)
      - Expert Oral 1 Cunnilingus B4, 2006-2007; DVD-2282 (Box 20)
      - Expert Oral 1 Cunnilingus B5, 2006-2007; DVD-2283 (Box 20)
      - Expert Oral 1 Cunnilingus B6, 2006-2007; DVD-2284 (Box 20)
      - Expert Oral 1 Cunnilingus B7, 2006-2007; DVD-2285 (Box 20)
      - Expert Oral 1 Cunnilingus Screener 2, 2007-05-01; DVD-2286 (Box 20)
      - Expert Oral 1 Cunnilingus Screener 3, 2007-05-09; DVD-2287 (Box 20)
      - Expert Oral 1 Cunnilingus Photos 1, 2006-2007; CD-3462 (Box 20)
      - Expert Oral 1 Cunnilingus Photos 2, 2006-2007; CD-3463; Octavio (Box 20)
        Talent IDs / Extra IDs / Workshop BTS
      - Expert Oral 1 Cunnilingus Photos 3, 2006-2007; CD-3464; Octavio (Box 20)
        Justine Pretty Girl / Justine + Ariel x Scene
      - Expert Anal Screener, 2007; DVD-2288; Octavio (Box 20)
        Ariel x Pretty Girls
      - Expert Anal Roughcut 2, 2007; DVD-2289 (Box 20)
      - Expert Anal Bonus Material, 2007; DVD-2290 (Box 20)
      - Expert Anal Audio, 2007; DVD-2291 (Box 20)
      - Expert Anal A1, 2007; DVD-2292 (Box 20)
      - Expert Anal A2, 2007; DVD-2293 (Box 20)
      - Expert Anal A3, 2007; DVD-2294 (Box 20)
      - Expert Anal A4, 2007; DVD-2295 (Box 20)
      - Expert Anal A5, 2007; DVD-2296 (Box 20)
      - Expert Anal B1, 2007; DVD-2297 (Box 20)
      - Expert Anal B2, 2007; DVD-2298 (Box 20)
      - Expert Anal B3, 2007; DVD-2299 (Box 20)
      - Expert Anal B4, 2007; DVD-2300 (Box 20)
      - Expert Anal B5, 2007; DVD-2301 (Box 20)
      - Expert Anal B6, 2007; DVD-2302 (Box 20)
      - 10/21/06 No. 1, 2006-10-21; CD-3465 (Box 20)
      - 10/21/06 No. 2, 2006-10-21; CD-3466 (Box 20)
      - 10/21/06 No. 3, 2006-10-21; CD-3467 (Box 20)
      - 10/21/06 No. 4, 2006-10-21; CD-3468 (Box 20)
      - Expert Positions for Tristan, 2008; DVD-2303 (Box 20)
      - Expert Positions Screener 2, 2008-04-24; DVD-2304 (Box 20)
      - Expert Positions, 2008-04-26; DVD-2305 (Box 20)
      - Kylee - Positions -"Multiple Mayhem", 2005-12-28; DVD-2306 (Box 20)
      - Lacie - Positions "Blonde Pretzel", 2005-12-29; DVD-2307 (Box 20)
      - Courtney - Positions "Courtney's Positions", 2006-05-05; DVD-2308 (Box 20)
      - Sandra - Positions "Sandra's Positions", 2006-05-05; DVD-2309 (Box 20)
      - Nakia - Positions "Blonde Babe Boogie", 2006-07-05; DVD-2310 (Box 20)
      - Roxy - Positions "Two Bows for Her Box", 2006-07-05; DVD-2311 (Box 20)
      - Sandra - Positions "When Booty Calls", 2006-07-05; DVD-2312 (Box 20)
      - Faith - Positions "Pleased to Meat You", 2006-07-08; DVD-2313 (Box 20)
      - Haley - Positions "Taking It to the Hole", 2006-07-08; DVD-2314 (Box 20)
      - Sandra - Positions "Any Wet Way You Can", 2006-07-08; DVD-2315 (Box 20)
      - Sandra - Positions "Let's Goo Two Rounds ", 2006-07-09; DVD-2316 (Box 20)
      - Celina - Positions "Beaver Fever", 2006-07-09; DVD-2317 (Box 20)
      - Faith - Positions "Frisky Business", 2006-07-09; DVD-2318 (Box 20)
      - Haley - Positions "Cum Bounce with Me", 2006-07-09; DVD-2319 (Box 20)
  - Other Films
    - Ultimate Guide to Anal Sex for Women production book, 1999-03-1999-08 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Ultimate Guide to Anal Sex for Women cover, 1999-06 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Ultimate Guide to Anal Sex for Women, 1999-06; V-9816-9817 (Box 9)
      Produced and directed by Tristan Taormino; includes two tapes
      Evil Angel
    - Ultimate Guide to Anal Sex for Women, 1999-06; DVD-2119 (Box 9)
      Produced and directed by Tristan Taormino
    - Ultimate Guide to Anal Sex for Women materials, 1999-06-2000 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Ultimate Guide to Anal Sex for Women 2 materials, 2001-03-2001-12 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Ultimate Guide to Anal Sex for Women 2, 2001-08-27; V-9808 (Box 9)
    - Ultimate Guide to Anal Sex for Women 2, 2005-08; DVD-2120 (Box 9)
    - House of Ass materials, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - House of Ass, 2006; V-9793 (Box 9)
    - House of Ass Deleted Scenes, 2006; V-9794 (Box 9)
    - House of Ass, 2006-01; DVD-2121 (Box 9)
      Directed by Tristan Taormino; signed by Tristan Taormino
      Adam & Eve Pictures
    - Guide to Kinky Sex for Couples, 2013; DVD-2122-2123 (Box 9)
  - She Hate Me
    - She Hate Me screenplay 1st revision, 2003; Genet, Michael; Lee, Spike (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Lesbian Boot Camp materials, 2003; Taormino, Tristan (Box 10, Folder 13)
      Lesbian 101 - A Crash Course was given by Taormino to educate the actresses
    - Spike Lee notes to Tristan Taormino, 2003-08-08-2003-09-14; Lee, Spike (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - She Hate Me materials, 2003-08-11-2004-03-08 (Box 10, Folder 15)
      Includes correspondence, consultant letter agreement, second round script revisions, Lesbian Boot Camp materials